Finding Aid for the Fletcher Bascom Dresslar Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Publications
  - Bulletins on school architecture & hygiene for the U.S. Office of Education
High School Commencement Ad undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 1 Marked
History of Education in Europe 1899 Cubberly, Ellwoo Publication 11 11 Syllabus
How Can County Schools Be Ma undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 2 Marked
How the Ellerbe Young Tar Heel undat Meacham, Arthu Typed Manuscri 11 12
How to Live Longer & Be Happy 1920 Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 2
How to Prevent Worry undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 11 9
Hutchinson, Kansas, High School undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 2
Hygiene of Teaching Language, undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 2
In Memoriam 1926 Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri Mark 10 2
Instructions Regarding Thesis W 1901 Leland Stanford Publication 11 12
Invest in Yourselves .... undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 11 3
Investigations Made in Departme undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 11 9
Janitor Service undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 2
Jesus as a Teacher undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 10 2
Left-Handedness undat LeMar, Esther Typed Manuscri 11 12
Lighting undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 2 Marked
Lighting of School Buildings undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 2 2 copies, one marked
List Board of Health Literature re undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 11 9
Location of School Buildings undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 3
Lowell High School undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 3
M.I.T. School Health Appraisal Fo undat Turner, C.E. Typed Manuscri 11 13
Manual Training undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 3
Marshall’s Pencils undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 11 4
Medical Inspection undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 3 2 copies
Medical Inspection of Schools undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 11 9
Memorial of Albert Homer Purdue 1918 Ashley, George Publication 11 11
Money for Rural Schools undat U.S. Department Publication 11 13
Morning’s Observation of a Baby, 1901 Dresslar, Fletch Publication 10 3
National Herbart Society undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 3 Marked
New Central High School, Minnea undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 3 2 copies, one marked
New Education undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 3 Marked
New High School Building, Green 1914 Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 3
New High School, South Bend, In undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 3 2 copies
New Method of Color Mixing, A undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 10 4
New Patriotism, A undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 11 4
New Psychology & its Pedagogic undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 10 4
Normality undat Meyer, Adelphia Typed Manuscri 11 12
North Dakota State Board of Heal 1918 Publication 11 10
Notes on Building Code for the St undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 4
Of Youth undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 4 Marked
On Boarding Schools 1907 Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 11 4
Open Air Schools undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri Mark 10 4
Organization & Supervision 1899 Cubberly, Ellwoo Publication 11 11 Syllabus
Organization of the Interstate Sch 1930 Dresslar, Fletch Publication 10 4 Article in “School Life”
Orientation undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 4 Marked
Orientation of Class Rooms undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 4 2 copies, one marked
Outline of Report of Study of Sch undat Dresslar, F.B. & Typed Manuscri Mark 10 4
Outline of the Hot Springs Summ undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 11 9
Peabody Reflector & Alumni New 1920 Publication 11 10
Physical Equipment for the Scho undat Library Commiss Publication 11 10
Playgrounds undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 4 2 copies, marked
Portable Houses undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 4
Possible Experiments undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 11 4 Notebook
Prayer undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 10 4
Press Release 1915 North Carolina S Publication 11 12
Principals undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 4
Projects in Sex Education undat McCanless, Eva Typed Manuscri 11 12
Psychology of Touch in General undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 10 5
Relation of Character to Good He undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 11 4
Religion, Dogmantism in Science undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 11 4
Religious Forces in Higher Educa 1900 Brown, Elmer Ell Publication 11 11
Report Survey Evanston, Illinois undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 5
Report of Joint Committees on H undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 5
Report of the Committee on Phys 1898 Council of Educ Publication 11 10
Report of the Survey of the High 1916 Brown, J. Stanle Typed Manuscri 11 11
Report on Standards for Element 1928 Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 5
Reports of Department Committe undat American Unitari Publication 11 10
Requirements & Standards to be undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 5
Rural School Hygiene 1914 Rapeer, Louis W Publication 11 13
School Architecture & Sanitation undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 5
School Building Decoration undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 6
School Buildings & Grounds undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 6
School Decoration undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 6
School Desks undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 10 6
School Sanitation undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 6
School as a Socializing Agency, undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 5 Marked
Sex Education undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 6
Sierra Educational News & Book 1911 Council of Educ Publication 11 10
Some Phases of Kindergarten Pr undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 10 6
Some Problems to be Considere undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 6
Some Suggestions Concerning D undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 6 Marked
State Supervision of School Archi undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 6
Study of Adolescence, The 1891 Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 11 5
Suggestions from the Psychology undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 11 5
Suggestions on Sketch Enclosed undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 11 6
Suggestions on the Need for Sani undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 6
Supervision of Teachers undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 7
Survey, The undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 7
Teacher, A Servant of the State, undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 7
Teachers undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 10 7
Tests & Measurements of Childre undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 10 7
The Future Location of City Scho undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 9 16
Theory & Practice undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 11 6
To What Extent are the School A undat Dresslar, Fletch Publication 11 9
To define means to limit.... undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 11 6
To the Board of Education of, Th 1910 Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 9 13
To the Members of the National undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 7
Toilets undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 7
Toilets undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 7
Trabajos de Higiene Escolar del 1920 Unidentified Publication 11 9
Two Evils of Modern Immigration undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 10 7
Tyranny of Tradition, The undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 8
Unidentified undat Unidentified Holograph Manu 11 13
Uniting the Home & School in He 1929 Whitney, Anne Publication 11 13
Untitled undat Franklin, W.S. Typed Manuscri 11 11
Use of Score Cards in School Bui undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 8 Marked
Value of Child Study to the Currie undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 8 Marked
Ventilation undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 11 6
Ventilation & Heating of the Stock 1907 Sundell, Carl Typed Manuscri 11 13 Outline
Vision Undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 11 6 Notecard
Voice in Spiritual Education, The undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 8 Marked
Volume on Superstition & Educati 1907 Sierra Education Publication 11 13
West Virginia University undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 8
What Parents Should Teach Thei undat Weir, H.C. Typed Manuscri 11 13
What the Adolescent Girl Should undat Jenkins, Mrs. Typed Manuscri 11 12
What the Appalachian Training S undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 11 6
Why I Plant a Garden undat Dresslar, Fletch Holograph Manu 11 6
Willys Knight 1927 Willys-Overland, Publication 11 10
Windows undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 8
Windows undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 8
Womanhood & Its Development undat Rummell, Luella Publication 11 9
Work Space for Children in Elem undat Dresslar, Fletch Typed Manuscri 10 8
Writings of Dr. Fletcher Bascom undat Pruett, Haskell Typed Manuscri 11 13 2 copies
DRESSOUT
Kalbach, L.A. Nov. 25, 1911 1
Carmichael, O.C. Dec. 11, 1912 1
Dearborn, George Van D. Dec. 11, 1912 1
Hume, Edward H. Dec. 11, 1912 1
Carrier Air Conditioning Co. Dec. 31, 1912 1
Claxton, P.P. Dec. 31, 1912 1
Goldsberry, L.D. Dec. 31, 1912 1
Holland, E.O. Dec. 31, 1912 1
McClain, E.L. Dec. 31, 1912 1
MA Sanitary Appliance Co. Dec. 31, 1912 1
Motyl, Joe Dec. 31, 1912 1
Claxton, P.P. 1912 1
Claxton, P.P. 1912 1
Claxton, P.P. Jan. 1, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Jan. 1, 1913 1
Ormsby, Carrie 0. Jan. 1, 1913 1
Brewster, Wales C. Jan. 3, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Jan. 3, 1913 1
DuShane, Daniel Jan. 3, 1913 1
King, Jennette M. Jan. 3, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. Jan. 3, 1913 1
Maphis, Charles G. Jan. 3, 1913 1
Page, Thomas Walker Jan. 3, 1913 1
Johnson, R.C. Jan. 8, 1913 1
Kingsley, S.C. Jan. 8, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. Jan. 8, 1913 1
Wehrhahn, Dr. Jan. 8, 1913 1
Challman, S.A. Jan. 10, 1913 1
Cheney, Charles Henry Jan. 13, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Jan. 13, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Jan. 13, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. Jan. 13, 1913 1
Norris, J.L. Jan. 13, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Jan. 14, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. Jan. 14, 1913 1
Storey, Thomas A. Jan. 13, 1913 1
Wood, Frank C. Jan. 14, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Jan. 15, 1913 1
Bureau of Education Jan. 18, 1913 1
Fisher, C.W. Jan. 18, 1913 1
Henry, J. Earl Jan. 18, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Jan. 18, 1913 1
Ludlow & Peabody Jan. 18, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. Jan. 18, 1913 1
Acme Asbestos Cover & Suppl Jan. 21, 1913 1
Brister, J.W. Jan. 21, 1913 1
Bruere, R.W. Jan. 21, 1913 1
Brewster, Wales C. Jan. 21, 1913 1
Doll, E.A. Jan. 21, 1913 1
Eggleston, J.D. Jan. 21, 1913 1
Goddard, H.H. Jan. 21, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Jan. 21, 1913 1
Hintrager, Carl Jan. 21, 1913 1
Voght, H.W. Jan. 21, 1913 1
Whitcomb, J.E. Jan. 21, 1913 1
Wilson, Louis N. Jan. 21, 1913 1
Woods, R.S. Jan. 21, 1913 1
Gram, Franklin C. Jan. 23, 1913 1
Little, R.I. Jan. 23, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. Jan. 23, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Jan. 24, 1913 1
Payne, Bruce R. Jan. 24, 1913 1
Claxton. P.P. Jan. 25, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Jan. 25, 1913 1
Johnson, D.B. Jan. 25, 1913 1
Rail, E.E. Jan. 25, 1913 1
Yasinski, A.F. Jan. 25, 1913 1
Acme Asbestos Cover & Suppl Jan. 27, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Jan. 27, 1913 1
Dahlstrom Metalic Door Co. Jan. 27, 1913 1
Palmer, T.W. Jan. 27, 1913 1
Devendorf, B.A. Jan. 28, 1913 1
Fisher, C.W. Jan. 28, 1913 1
Judd, Zebulon Jan. 28, 1913 1
Morris, Agnes Jan. 28, 1913 1
Rail, E.E. Jan. 28, 1913 1
Atlas School Supply Co. Jan. 29, 1913 1
Brewster, Wales C. Jan. 29, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Jan. 29, 1913 1
Hood, W.R. Jan. 29, 1913 1
Hood, W.R. Jan. 29, 1913 1
Merritt & Co. Jan. 29, 1913 1
Monroe, Paul Jan. 29, 1913 1
Rail, E.E. Jan. 29, 1913 1
Yasinski, A.F. Jan. 29, 1913 1
Foght, H.W. Jan. 31, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Jan. 31, 1913 1
Thesmar, Alix Jan. 31, 1913 1
Boykin, J.C. Feb. 1, 1913 1
Brewster, Wales C. Feb. 1, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Feb. 1, 1913 1
Ittner, W.B. Feb. 1, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Feb. 1, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. Feb. 1, 1913 1
Canfield, George Feb. 3, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. Feb. 3, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. Feb. 3, 1913 1
Yasinski, A.F. Feb. 3, 1913 1
Boykin, J.C. Feb. 5, 1913 1
Cooper, Frank Irving Feb. 5, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Feb. 5, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Feb. 5, 1913 1
Dry, M.B. Feb. 6, 1913 1
Glaniel, M.M. Feb. 6, 1913 1
Henry, J. Earl Feb. 6, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. Feb. 6, 1913 1
Rail, E.E. Feb. 6, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Feb. 7, 1913 1
Dowling, Oscar Feb. 7, 1913 1
Ittner, W.B. Feb. 7, 1913 1
Judd, Zebulon Feb. 7, 1913 1
Morris, Agnes Feb. 7, 1913 1
Byerly, H.E. Feb. 8, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. Feb. 8, 1913 1
Rail, E.E. Feb. 8, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Feb. 10, 1913 1
Rail, E.E. Feb. 10, 1913 1
Yasinski, A.Y. Feb. 11, 1913 1
Henry, J. Earl Feb. 12, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Feb. 13, 1913 1
Kennedy, D.C. Feb. 14, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. Feb. 14, 1913 1
Rail, E.E. Feb. 14, 1913 1
Wolcott, J.D. Feb. 14, 1913 1
Doll, E.A. Feb. 15, 1913 1
Ittner, William B. Feb. 15, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. Feb. 15, 1913 1
Brewster, W.C. Feb. 17, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Feb. 17, 1913 1
Doii,A.E. Feb. 17, 1913 1
Blair, Francis G. Feb. 21, 1913 1
Brewster, W.C. Feb. 21, 1913 1
Hyatt, Edward Feb. 21, 1913 1
McCloskey, Alice G. Feb. 21, 1913 1
Swearinger, J.E. Feb. 21, 1913 1
Yasinski, A.F. Feb. 21, 1913 1
Kentucky State Board of Health Feb. 22, 1913 1
Doll, E.A. Feb. 27, 1913 1
Fisher, C.W. Feb. 27, 1913 1
Blair, Francis G. March 1, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. March 1, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. March 1, 1913 1
Mark, E.H. March 1, 1913 1
Swearingen, J.E. March 1, 1913 1
van Hoose, A.W. March 1, 1913 1
Weinzirl, John March 1, 1913 1
Doster, James P. March 4, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. March 4, 1913 1
McClain, E.L. March 4, 1913 1
Mark, E.H. March 5, 1913 1
Yasinski, A.Y. March 7, 1913 1
Barnes, Earl March 8, 1913 1
Booker, Warren H. March 8, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. March 8, 1913 1
Gregg, F.M. March 8, 1913 1
Jones, S.B. March 8, 1913 1
Roach, Walter W. March 8, 1913 1
Wood, Thomas D. March 8, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. March 10, 191 1
Corwin, R.W. March 10, 191 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. March 10, 191 1
Ittner, William B. March 10, 191 1
McClain, E.L. March 10, 191 1
Cheney, Charles Henry March 11, 191 1
Claxton, P.P. March 11, 191 1
Foster, James H. March 11, 191 1
Mark, E.H. March 11, 191 1
Payne, Bruce R. March 11, 191 1
Backus, Emma S. March 12, 191 1
Bruce, William G. March 12, 191 1
Claxton, P.P. March 12, 191 1
Phelps, Jessie March 12, 191 1
Wood, Thomas D. March 12, 191 1
Yasinski, A.Y. March 12, 191 1
Brewster, W.C. March 13, 191 1
Jones, S.B. March 13, 191 1
Ittner, William B. March 14, 191 1
McClain, E.L. March 14, 191 1
Wood, Thomas D. March 14, 191 1
Ferguson, Calrow & Taylor March 15, 191 1
Burton Range Company March 17, 191 1
Frank A. Hall & Sons March 17, 191 1
Maphis, Charles G. March 17, 191 1
Richmond Adjustable Window March 17, 191 1
Ludlow & Peabody March 21, 191 1
McClain, E.L. March 21, 191 1
Comins, H.M. March 22, 191 1
Green, Frederick R. March 22, 191 1
McCloskey, Alice G. March 22, 191 1
Maphis, Charles G. March 22, 191 1
Stevenson, T.J. March 22, 191 1
Taylor, R.E. Lee March 22, 191 1
Wood, Thomas D. March 22, 191 1
Claxton, P.P. March 24, 191 1
Kalbach, L.A. March 24, 191 1
McCullough, J.E. March 24, 191 1
Wood, Thomas D. March 24, 191 1
Fisher, C.W. March 25, 191 1
Postman, J.K. March 25, 191 1
Cheney, Charles J. March 27, 191 1
Green, Frederick R. March 27, 191 1
Keith, James March 27, 191 1
Speed, James March 27, 191 1
Yasinski, A.F. March 27, 191 1
Ittner, William B. March 28, 191 1
McClain, E.L. March 28, 191 1
Wood, Thomas D. March 28, 191 1
Doelle, Jonathan A. March 29, 191 1
Rail, R.E. March 29, 191 1
Wolcott, Jonathan D. March 29, 191 1
McClain, E.L. Oct. 8, 1913 1
Narramore, F.A. Oct. 8, 1913 1
Brown, Henry E. Oct. 30, 1913 1
Carter, H.E. Oct. 30, 1913 1
Challman, S.A. Oct. 30, 1913 1
Crosier, M.E. Oct. 30, 1913 1
Downes, F.E. Oct. 30, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Oct. 30, 1913 1
Kingsley, Sherman C. Oct. 30, 1913 1
Rasor, Alpha Oct. 30, 1913 1
Thackston, John A. Oct. 30, 1913 1
Doster, James J. Nov. 1, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Nov. 1, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Nov. 1, 1913 1
Lamson, Ernest Nov. 1, 1913 1
Wray, George B. Nov. 1, 1913 1
Grand Rapids Hand Screw Co. Nov. 3, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Nov. 3, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Nov. 5, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Nov. 5, 1913 1
Mcintire, Charles Nov. 5, 1913 1
Rasor, Alpha Nov. 5, 1913 1
Sheats, W.N. Nov. 5, 1913 1
Sweeney, Mary E. Nov. 5, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Nov. 6, 1913 1
Hill, David Spence Nov. 7, 1913 1
Storey, Thomas A. Nov. 7, 1913 1
Boykin, J.C. Nov. 8, 1913 1
Burnham, George, Jr. Nov. 8, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Nov. 8, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Nov. 8, 1913 1
Kingsley, Sherman C. Nov. 8, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Nov. 10, 1913 1
Jennings, E.H. Nov. 10, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Nov. 10, 1913 1
Lamson, Ernest Nov. 10, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Nov. 11, 1913 1
Lull, Herbert W. Nov. 11, 1913 1
Moore, Wilmer L. Nov. 11, 1913 1
Parrott, Hattie Nov. 11, 1913 1
Cooper, Frank Irving Nov. 12, 1913 1
Kline, L.M. Nov. 12, 1913 1
Perkins, Fellows & Hamilton Nov. 12, 1913 1
Rasor, Alpha Nov. 12, 1914 1
Rowell, Percy E. Nov. 12, 1913 1
Wilson, R.H. Nov. 13, 1914 1
Bancroft, Jessie H. Nov. 14, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Nov. 14, 1913 1
Henry, J. Earl Nov. 14, 1913 1
Kilham, W.H. Nov. 14, 1913 1
McConnell, H.B. Nov. 14, 1913 1
Storey, Thomas A. Nov. 14, 1913 1
Boykin, J.C. Nov. 15, 1913 1
Richmond, Frank C. Nov. 15, 1913 1
Ellis, Dr. Nov. 17, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Nov. 17, 1913 1
Waterman-Waterbury Co. Nov. 17, 1913 1
Wood, Thomas D. Nov. 17, 1913 1
Lull, Herbert W. Nov. 18, 1913 1
McCormack, A.T. Nov. 18, 1913 1
Wetzel, William A. Nov. 18, 1913 1
Edwards, William A. Nov. 19, 1913 1
Ferrell, John A. Nov. 19, 1913 1
McDonald, A.A. Nov. 19, 1913 1
Callahan, E.B. Nov. 20, 1913 1
Hill, David Spence Nov. 20, 1913 1
McCormack, A.T. Nov. 20, 1913 1
Wilson, Louis N. Nov. 20, 1913 1
Wray, George B. Nov. 20, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Nov. 21, 1913 1
Avery, Lewis B. Nov. 24, 1913 1
Babbitt, Ellen C. Nov. 24, 1913 1
Cady, Bertha Chapman Nov. 24, 1913 1
Challman, S.A. Nov. 24, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Nov. 24, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Nov. 24, 1913 1
Corwin, R.W. Nov. 24, 1913 1
Kingsley, Sherman C. Nov. 24, 1913 1
Salley, Nathaniel Moss Nov. 24, 1913 1
Beard, Harrington Nov. 26, 1913 1
Boykin, J.C. Nov. 28, 1913 1
Ittner, William B. Nov. 28, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Nov. 28, 1913 1
Kelsey, William B. Nov. 28, 1913 1
Naramore, F.A. Nov. 28, 1913 1
Wood, Thomas D. Nov. 28, 1913 1
Boykin, J.C. Nov. 29, 1913 1
Waterman-Waterbury Co. Nov. 29, 1913 1
Corwin, R.W. Dec. 1, 1913 1
Courtis, S.A. Dec. 1, 1913 1
Ferrell, John A. Dec. 1, 1913 1
Hauer, Harvey T. Dec. 1, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Dec. 1, 1913 1
Lamson, Ernest Dec. 1, 1913 1
Lowe, L.L. Dec. 1, 1913 1
Miller, Frank W. Dec. 1, 1913 1
Platt, J. Mills Dec. 1, 1913 1
Naramore, F.A. Dec. 2, 1913 1
Wood, Thomas D. Dec. 4, 1913 1
Corwin, R.W. Dec. 5, 1913 1
Feagin, William F. Dec. 5, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Dec. 5, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Dec. 5, 1913 1
Preston, Mrs. J.T. Dec. 5, 1913 1
Summers, Alexander Dec. 5, 1913 1
Tate, W.K. Dec. 5, 1913 1
Wood, Thomas D. Dec. 5, 1913 1
Boykin, J.C. Dec. 6, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Dec. 8, 1913 1
Siebert, Victor E. Dec. 8, 1913 1
Waterman-Waterbury Co. Dec. 8, 1913 1
Coblentz, H.E. Dec. 9, 1913 1
F.A. Davis Co. Dec. 9, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Dec. 9, 1913 1
Taylor, H.L. Dec. 9, 1913 1
Thomas, R.H. Dec. 9, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Dec. 10, 1913 1
Tate, W.K. Dec. 10, 1913 1
Boykin, J.C. Dec. 11, 1913 1
Foster, James H. Dec. 11, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Dec. 11, 1913 1
Summers, Alexander Dec. 11, 1913 1
Wood, Thomas D. Dec. 11, 1913 1
Ambrose, Margaret A. Dec. 12, 1913 1
Haskins, C. Dec. 12, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Dec. 12, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Dec. 12, 1913 1
Linn & McCabe Dec. 12, 1913 1
McCloskey, Alice Dec. 12, 1913 1
Macon County Superintendent Dec. 12, 1913 1
Morrison, J.H.S. Dec. 12, 1913 1
Patton, Ruby Dec. 12, 1913 1
Teacher, Cross Roads School Dec. 12, 1913 1
Teacher, Cross Roads School Dec. 12, 1913 1
American Sanitary Products Co Dec. 13, 1913 1
Babbitt, Ellen C. Dec. 13, 1913 1
Challman, S.A. Dec. 13, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Dec. 13, 1913 1
Gier & Dail Manufacturing Co. Dec. 13, 1913 1
Hamrick-Tobey Co. Dec. 13, 1913 1
Mahoney Fountain Company Dec. 13, 1913 1
Murdock Manufacturing & Supp Dec. 13, 1913 1
Boykin, J.C. Dec. 15, 1913 1
Ellis, Carlos B. Dec. 15, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Dec. 15, 1913 1
Howell, Harry Dec. 15, 1913 1
Kalbach, L.A. Dec. 15, 1913 1
Linn-McCabe Co. Dec. 15, 1913 1
Preston, Josephine Dec. 15, 1913 1
Wood, Thomas D. Dec. 17, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Dec. 18, 1913 1
Weeks, William H. Dec. 18, 1913 1
Ludlow & Peabody Dec. 19, 1913 1
Preston, Josephine Dec. 20, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Dec. 20, 1913 1
Wood, Thomas D. Dec. 20, 1913 1
Aspinwall, William B. Dec. 22, 1913 1
Goldsberry, Louise D. Dec. 22, 1913 1
Haskins, C.A. Dec. 22, 1913 1
Kingsley, Sherman C. Dec. 22, 1913 1
McCloskey, Alice G. Dec. 22, 1913 1
Moulthrop, S.P. Dec. 22, 1913 1
Strong, Edward K., Jr. Dec. 22, 1913 1
Boykin, J.C. Dec. 24, 1913 1
Claxton, P.P. Dec. 24, 1913 1
Kingsley, Sherman C. Dec. 24, 1913 1
Linn-McCabe Co. Dec. 24, 1913 1
Aspinwall, William B. Jan. 9, 1914 2
Claxton, P.P. Jan. 9, 1914 2
Goldsberry, Louise D. Jan. 9, 1914 2
Haskins, C.A. Jan. 9, 1914 2
McClain, E.L. Jan. 9, 1914 2
McElveen, W.T. Jan. 9, 1914 2
Taylor, H.L. Jan. 9, 1914 2
Kingsley, S.C. Jan. 10, 1914 2
Claxton, P.P. Jan. 12, 1914 2
McElveen, W.T. Jan. 12, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Jan. 13, 1914 2
Claxton, P.P. Jan. 14, 1913 2
Kegley, E.S. Jan. 14, 1914 2
McElveen, W.T. Jan. 14, 1914 2
Feagin, William F. Jan. 15, 1914 2
Boykin, J.C. Jan. 16, 1914 2
Claxton, P.P. Jan. 16, 1914 2
Feagin, William F. Jan. 16, 1914 2
Grim, J.S. Jan. 16, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Jan. 17, 1914 2
Wood, Thomas D. Jan. 17, 1914 2
Cheney, May L. Jan. 19, 1914 2
Keene, Charles H. Jan. 19, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Jan. 19, 1914 2
Love, N.N. Jan. 19, 1914 2
Claxton, P.P. Jan. 20, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Jan. 21, 1914 2
McNierney, A. Jan. 21, 1914 2
Smith, D.S. Jan. 22, 1914 2
Boykin, J.C. Jan. 23, 1914 2
Goldsberry, Louise D. Jan. 23, 1914 2
Boykin, J.C. Jan. 24, 1914 2
Boykin, J.C. Jan. 24, 1914 2
Grim, J.G. Jan. 24, 1914 2
Jones, W.H. Jan. 24, 1914 2
Boykin, J.C. Feb. 4, 1914 2
Challman, S.A. Feb. 4, 1914 2
Claxton, P.P. Feb. 4, 1914 2
Keene, Charles H. Feb. 4, 1914 2
Ocker, W.A. Feb. 4, 1914 2
Wood, Thomas D. Feb. 4, 1914 2
Castle, Cora Sutton Feb. 5, 1914 2
Goldsberry, Louise D. Feb. 5, 1914 2
Love, N.N. Feb. 5, 1914 2
Nelson, E.G. Feb. 5, 1914 2
Wood, Thomas D. Feb. 5, 1914 2
Hefferan, Mrs. W.J. Feb. 6, 1914 2
LeGarde, Ellen Feb. 6, 1914 2
U.S. Public Health Service Feb. 6, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Feb. 9, 1914 2
McBrien, J.L. Feb. 9, 1914 2
Claxton, P.P. Feb. 9, 1914 2
Unidentified Feb. 9, 1914 2
Burfitt, L.R. Godfrey Feb. 11, 1914 2
Goldey, Stanley Feb. 11, 1914 2
Hobart, Louis P. Feb. 11, 1914 2
McElveen, W.T. Feb. 11, 1914 2
Bryan, E.B. Feb. 12, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Feb. 12, 1914 2
Boykin, J.C. Feb. 13, 1914 2
McCarnock, W.R. Feb. 14, 1914 2
Ryan, W. Carson, Jr. Feb. 14, 1914 2
Boykin, J.C. Feb. 16, 1914 2
Bruce, William C. Feb. 16, 1914 2
Feagin, W.F. Feb. 16, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Feb. 16, 1914 2
Naramore, F.A. Feb. 16, 1914 2
Perkins, Fellows & Hamilton Feb. 17, 1914 2
Adee, John A. Feb. 19, 1914 2
Boykin, J.C. Feb. 20, 1914 2
Claxton, P.P. Feb. 20, 1914 2
Kingsley, Sherman C. Feb. 20, 1914 2
Central Commercical & Manual Feb. 20, 1914 2
Wood, Thomas D. Feb. 20, 1914 2
Boykin, J.C. Feb. 21, 1914 2
Aspinwall, W.B. Feb. 23, 1914 2
Boehm, Peter J. Feb. 23, 1914 2
Boykin, J.C. Feb. 23, 1914 2
Burton, E.D. Feb. 23, 1914 2
Goetze, F.A. Feb. 23, 1914 2
Hirdansky, Simon Feb. 23, 1914 2
Perkins, D.H. Feb. 23, 1914 2
Van Rennselaer, Martha Feb. 23, 1914 2
Bruce, William C. Feb. 24, 1914 2
Claxton, P.P. Feb. 24, 1914 2
Saunderson, M.A. Feb. 25, 1914 2
Blewett, Ben Feb. 27, 1914 2
Boykin, J.C. March 2, 1914 2
Feagin, William F. March 5, 1914 2
Bogan, William J. March 6, 1914 2
Alderman, L.R. March 9, 1914 2
McNutt, Randolph March 9, 1914 2
American Seating Company March 13, 191 2
American Seating Company March 16, 191 2
Atlas School Supply Co. March 16, 191 2
Atlas School Supply Co. March 16, 191 2